Finding Aid for the Han Yu-Shan Collection LSC.1372
UCLA Library Special Collections
Han Yu-Shan collection
1646-1910
UCLA Library Special Collections
Han, Yu-shan
LSC.1372
7.5 Linear Feet (15 boxes and 21 oversize boxes)
Yu-shan Han (1899-1983) taught at the History Department, UCLA (1941 to 1966). The collection consists of 24 histories of academies in China published between 1684-1910, a printed text of the Diamond Sutra (1798), a set of original woodblocks for the Diamond Sutra, imperial examination papers (1646-1904), imperial edicts, and manuscript scrolls.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Examination papers available on microfilm (6 reels) in UCLA Library Special Collections (collection 1372, box 36) and East Asian Library, UCLA. Originals not available for consultation due to fragile condition.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Edna and Yu-shan Han Charitable Foundation, 1984.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9914707383606533
Biography
Born in Peking, China; Ph.D. from Boston University, 1929; taught at History Department, UCLA, from 1941 to 1966.
Scope and Content
Consists of 24 histories of academies (shu yüan) in China, published 1684-1910; printed text of the Diamond Sutra (Chin kang ching), 1798; a set of original woodblocks for the Diamond Sutra; approximately 500 imperial examination papers from 1646 to 1904--ca. 300 palace examinations (tien shih) papers (including 39 Manchu language examinations and 5 military examinations), 97 academy examinations, and other miscellaneous examinations; as well as some imperial edicts and manuscript scrolls.
Organization and Arrangement
Organized into histories of academies, 1684-1910 (3 boxes); printed text of the Diamond Sutra (Chin kang ching), 1798 (8 boxes); set of original woodblocks for the Diamond Sutra (4 boxes); imperial examination papers, 1646-1904 (18 boxes); and microfilms of the imperial examination papers (2 boxes).
Examination papers are organized into 8 groups:
Palace examinations with names.
Anomymous palace examinations.
Palace examinations by subject.
Palace poetry examinations.
Palace Manchu language examinations.
Academy examinations.
Miscellaneous examinations.
Palace military examinations.
Chronological arrangement within each group if dates are known.
China History -- Qing dynasty, 1644-1912 -- Examinations, questions, etc.; Learned institutions and societies -- China -- History.; Chinese examination essays.; Civil service -- China -- Examinations, questions, etc.
- Histories and Other Publications of Academies
  - Jing xin shu yuan ji, volume 4., 1889.; Item no. 1 (Box 1)
  - Jing xin shu yuan xu ji, volume 6., 1895.; Item no. 2 (Box 1)
  - Zhong wu shu yuan tiao gui, volume 1., 1842.; Item no. 1 (Box 2)
  - Hai dong shu yuan ke yi, volume 4., 1892.; Item no. 2 (Box 2)
  - Xin jiang shu yuan zhi, volume 4., 1867.; Item no. 1 (Box 3)
  - Hunan Changsha Fu Yiyang Xian Zhen yan shu yuan zhi, volume 3., 1866.; Item no. 2 (Box 3)
  - Yi shan shu yuan zhi, volume 2., 1843.; Item no. 1 (Box 4)
  - Lian xi zhi, volume 4., 1839.; Item no. 2 (Box 4)
  - Lian shan shu yuan zhi, volume 2., 1709?.; Item no. 3 (Box 4)
  - Long shan shu yuan ke yi, volume 4., 1870.; Item no. 1 (Box 5)
  - Ming dao shu yuan chao cun, volume 4., 1899?.; Item no. 2 (Box 5)
  - Ming dao shu yaun ji ji, volume 2., 1707.; Item no. 3 (Box 5)
  - Nan jing xue yue, volume 1., 1904.; Item no. 1 (Box 6)
  - Nan xi shu yuan zhi, volume 4., 1870.; Item no. 2 (Box 6)
  - Nan yang shu yuan xue gui, volume 2., 1693.; Item no. 3 (Box 6)
  - Bai lu shu yuan zhi, volume 4., 1720.; Item no. 4 (Box 6)
  - Bai lu shu yuan zhi, volume 8., 1910. (Box 7)
  - Bao jin shu yuan zhi, volume 2., 1880.; Item no. 1 (Box 8)
  - Bian li yuan zhi, volume 3., 1830.; Item no. 2 (Box 8)
  - Zun jing shu yuan chu ji, volume 10., 1885. (Box 9)
  - Song yang shu yuan zhi, volume 2., 1701.; Item no. 4 (Box 8)
  - Song yang shu yuan zhi, volume 2., 1701.; Item no. 4 (Box 9)
  - Zun jing shu yuan chu ji, volume 10., 1885. (Box 10)
  - Dong lin shu yuan zhi, volume 8., 1881. (Box 10)
  - Yin shan shu yuan zhi, volume 4., 1774.; Item no. 1 (Box 11)
  - Xin xiu yue lu shu yuan zhi shu, volume 6., 1687.; Item no. 2 (Box 11)
  - Set of original woodblocks for the Diamond Sutra (Jin gang jing) (Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15)
- Palace Examination papers by Year
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Yinzhen, 1646; R1-1; Province: Shandong Age: 22 Rank: 3 no.127. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lu Yuanlong, 1647; R1-2; Province: Zhejiang Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.48. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhu Tianning, 1647; R1-3; Province: Jiangxi Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.9. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiao Shifen, 1649; R1-4; Province: Zhili Age: 26 Rank: 3 no.171. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Qian Kaizong, 1652; R1-5; Province: Zhejiang Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.124. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yao Qishen, 1655; R1-6; Province: Red Banner Age: 24 Rank: 3 no.84. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: You Shixi, 1655; R1-7; Province: Zhejiang Age: 22 Rank: 3 no.48. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ma Mingluan, 1673; R1-8; Province: Jiangnan Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.29. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiang Yiluan, 1688; R1-9; Province: Jiangnan Age: 44 Rank: 2 no.6. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Fahai, 1694; R1-10; Province: Yellow Banner Age: 25 Rank: 3 no.107. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Saodazi, 1706; R1-11; Province: Blue Banner Age: 32 Rank: 3 no.228. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Mengxu, 1712; R1-12; Province: Guizhou Age: 22 Rank: 3 no.80. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zheng Zhiqiao, 1712; R1-13; Province: Sichuan Age: 20 Rank: 3 no.89. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zha Xiang, 1718; R1-14; Province: Zhejiang Age: 45 Rank: 2 no.3. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang mengyao, 1718; R1-15; Province: Guizhou Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.85. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cheng Renqi, 1721; R1-16; Province: Guizhou Age: 19 Rank: 2 no.4. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Duanshen, 1721; R1-17; Province: Jiangnan Age: 39 Rank: 2 no.32. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Luo Migao, 1727; R1-18; Province: Sichuan Age: 34 Rank: 3 no.136. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Xianjing, 1729; R1-19; Province: Guizhou Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.220. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Dai Rufen, 1730; R1-20; Province: Shandong Age: 24 Rank: 2 no.12. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yin Zuyi, 1730; R1-21; Province: Guizhou Age: 46 Rank: 3 no.270. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Yinpei, 1745; R1-22; Province: Yunnan Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.9. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liang Changshen, 1761; R1-24; Province: Guangdong Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.10. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhu Delin, 1763; R1-25; Province: Zhejiang Age: 19 Rank: 2 no.4. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: He Dejun, 1769; R1-26; Province: Guizhou Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.48. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Shenhe, 1775; R1-27; Province: Fujian Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.4. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wei Chengxian, 1784; R1-28; Province: Zhejiang Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.4. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Tingfen, 1784; R1-29; Province: Zhili Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.5. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Feng Xishen, 1787; R1-30; Province: Jiangnan Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.23. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: He Mi, 1787; R1-31; Province: Guizhou Age: 35 Rank: 2 no.25. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Weiqi, 1787; R1-32; Province: Jiangnan Age: 37 Rank: 2 no.21. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Peixiang, 1793; R1-33; Province: Jiangnan Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.17. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Yuan, 1793; R1-34; Province: Shandong Age: 38 Rank: 2 no.10. (Box 16)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Yinlian, 1795; R1-23; Province: Jiangxi Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.18. (Box 16)
    General note
    (Microfilm number sequence changed due to correction of exam year)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tao Tingyang, 1801; R1-35; Province: Guizhou Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.117. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Tingjian, 1801; R1-36; Province: Shanxi Age: 26 Rank: 3 no.14. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: He Yingjie, 1802; R1-37; Province: Guizhou Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.16. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Kong Jihou, 1802; R1-38; Province: Shandong Age: 36 Rank: 3 no.146. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tao Siyong, 1802; R1-39; Province: Sichuan Age: 32 Rank: 3 no.145. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Deng Chuan'an, 1805; R1-40; Province: Jiangxi Age: 43 Rank: 3 no.3. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Fu Zhongchuan, 1808; R1-41; Province: Hunan Age: 25 Rank: 3 no.24. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiao Yingquan, 1808; R1-42; Province: Jiangxi Age: 33 Rank: 2 no.3. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Zhongmo, 1809; R1-43; Province: Jiangxi Age: 35 Rank: 2 no.8. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tan Xifu, 1811; R1-44; Province: Yunnan Age: 38 Rank: 3 no.136. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Zengfang, 1811; R1-45; Province: Jiangxi Age: 29 Rank: 2 no.5. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tao Tingjie, 1814; R1-46; Province: Guizhou Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.25. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Shi, 1814; R1-47; Province: Yunnan Age: 35 Rank: 3 no.36. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xu Peishen, 1817; R1-48; Province: Guizhou Age: 40 Rank: 2 no.12. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xu Jiudao, 1819; R1-49; Province: Guizhou Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.75. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: He Guixin, 1820; R1-50; Province: Jiangsu Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.2. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Zuoyi, 1820; R1-51; Province: Jiangxi Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.4. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Peng Zong, 1822; R1-52; Province: Guizhou Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.8. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Jun, 1822; R1-53; Province: Zhejiang Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.12. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Shen, 1822; R1-54; Province: Jiangsu Age: 21 Rank: 2 no.68. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Yaoting, 1822; R1-55; Province: Hubei Age: 34 Rank: 2 no.16. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhen Houguang, 1826; R1-56; Province: Guizhou Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.2. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Changzhi, 1826; R1-57; Province: Hubei Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.51. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Biao, 1826; R1-58; Province: Hubei Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.100. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Di Ting, 1829; R1-59; Province: Jiangsu Age: 35/53? Rank: 2 no.7. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yang Zhaojin, 1829; R1-60; Province: Hubei Age: 40 Rank: 3 no.60. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Baohe, 1835; R1-61; Province: Zhejiang Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.53. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Yuqi, 1835; R1-62; Province: Hubei Age: 35 Rank: 3 no.67. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Shouxun, 1835; R1-63; Province: Jiangxi Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.29. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liu Dejun, 1835; R1-64; Province: Hubei Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.91. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liu Mingben, 1835; R1-65; Province: Hubei Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.89. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Siyin, 1835; R1-66; Province: Hubei Age: 43 Rank: 3 no.73. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yan Qingyuan, 1835; R1-67; Province: Shanxi Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.67. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ye Weigui, 1835; R1-68; Province: Hubei Age: 35 Rank: 2 no.31. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ding Yunzhang, 1836; R1-69; Province: Hubei Age: 28 Rank: 3 no.60. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Shaofang, 1836; R1-70; Province: Fujian Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.70. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liu Yingdan, 1836; R1-71; Province: Hubei Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.39. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Mei Tang, 1836; R1-72; Province: Jiangxi Age: 22 Rank: 2 no.71. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xu Wenzhao, 1836; R1-73; Province: Zhejiang Age: 24 Rank: 2 no.9. (Box 17)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Zhaoxi, 1838; R1-74; Province: Jiangsu Age: 39 Rank: 3 no.109. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Yuanyan, 1838; R1-75; Province: Hu'nan Age: 23 Rank: 2 no.34. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Shi Zhanqing, 1838; R1-76; Province: Guizhou Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.24. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiao Shifu, 1840; R1-77; Province: Guizhou Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.52. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiong Cankui, 1840; R1-78; Province: Guizhou Age: 23 Rank: 3 no.73. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhu Zheng, 1840; R1-79; Province: Guizhou Age: 29 Rank: 3 no.49. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yu Futing, 1844; R1-80; Province: Guizhou Age: 27 Rank: 3 no.39. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cao Bingxie, 1845; R1-81; Province: Jiangsu Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.97. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lu Huang, 1845; R1-82; Province: Guizhou Age: 32 Rank: 2 no.29. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ren Dianxuan, 1845; R1-83; Province: Hubei Age: 42 Rank: 3 no.92. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Changshou, 1845; R1-84; Province: Zhejiang Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.72. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lu Bingshu, 1847; R1-85; Province: Zhejiang Age: 24 Rank: 2 no.9. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Kou Jiaxiang, 1850; R1-86; Province: Guizhou Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.82. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Daoyong, 1850; R1-87; Province: Hubei Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.71. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Lanfang, 1850; R1-88; Province: Guizhou Age: 23 Rank: 2 no.62. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ye Binghua, 1850; R1-89; Province: Guangdong Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.46. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhong Peixian, 1850; R2-1; Province: Zhili Age: 28 Rank: 3 no.44. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Jiang Qingdi, 1852; R2-2; Province: Zhili Age: 27 Rank: 2 no.69. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xie Jingao, 1852; R2-3; Province: Guizhou Age: 44 Rank: 2 no.91. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Yongkang, 1852; R2-4; Province: Guizhou Age: 18 Rank: 2 no.95. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Shen Zujian, 1853; R1-5; Province: Zhejiang Age: 32 Rank: 2 no.2. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Hongzuo, 1854; R1-6; Province: Guizhou Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.67. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lou Zhen, 1859; R2-7; Province: Zhejiang Age: 32 Rank: 2 no.12. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: He Ding, 1860; R2-8; Province: Guizhou Age: 34 Rank: 2 no.76. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: He Qing'en, 1860; R2-9; Province: Guizhou Age: 29 Rank: 3 no.74. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xie Shutang, 1863; R2-10; Province: Guangxi Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.23. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Weihan, 1863; R2-11; Province: Guangxi Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.27. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cao Changqi, 1871; R2-12; Province: Hunan Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.73. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Jie, 1871; R2-13; Province: Guizhou Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.93. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Luo Wenbin, 1871; R2-14; Province: Guizhou Age: 23 Rank: 2 no.36. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xie Yuanfu, 1871; R2-15; Province: Guangxi Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.8. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ren Guizhen, 1874; R2-16; Province: Hunan Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.27. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wulabu, 1874; R2-17; Province: Yellow Banner Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.75. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiao Shendou, 1874; R2-18; Province: Guizhou Age: 18 Rank: 3 no.163. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Zongding, 1874; R2-19; Province: Guizhou Age: 41 Rank: 3 no.2. (Box 18)
  - Exam Year: Name: An Yongsong, 1876; R2-20; Province: Guizhou Age: 32 Rank: 3 no.20. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Shuxun, 1876; R3-38; Province: Shaanxi Age: ?? Rank: 2 no.41 (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Sixiang, 1876; R2-21; Province: Yunnan Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.107. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Guojin, 1876; R2-22; Province: Guizhou Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.24. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Yi'nian, 1876; R2-23; Province: Henan Age: 27 Rank: 2 no.43. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lin Qi, 1876; R2-24; Province: Fujian Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.93. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Zhujing, 1876; R2-25; Province: Guizhou Age: 24 Rank: 2 no.47. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhou Zhao, 1876; R2-26; Province: Guizhou Age: 42 Rank: 2 no.111. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Chongguang, 1877; R2-27; Province: Shaanxi Age: 24 Rank: 3 no.26. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Tianxi, 1877; R2-28; Province: Guizhou Age: 33 Rank: 3 no.167. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Pan Wenxiong, 1877; R2-29; Province: Guizhou Age: 34 Rank: 2 no.107. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang En'gui, 1877; R2-30; Province: Zhili Age: 27 Rank: 3 no.47. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xu Daokun, 1877; R2-32; Province: Jiangxi Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.25. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yang Tiaoyuan, 1877; R2-33; Province: Guizhou Age: 22 Rank: 2 no.43. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yu Tao, 1877; R2-34; Province: Guizhou Age: 43 Rank: 3 no.169. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhong Dakun, 1877; R2-35; Province: Fujian Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.35. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Du Qingyuan, 1880; R2-36; Province: Guizhou Age: 24 Rank: 2 no.66. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xie Tingze, 1880; R2-31; Province: Guizhou Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.109 (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Chengcai, 1880; R2-37; Province: Jiangxi Age: 35 Rank: 3 no.125. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Debing, 1880; R2-38; Province: He'nan Age: 26 Rank: 2 no.22. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lian Peiji, 1880; R2-39; Province: Jiangxi Age: 29 Rank: 3 no.13. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Jingshi, 1880; R2-40; Province: Anhui Age: 25 Rank: 2 no.36. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liu Mingyu, 1880; R2-42; Province: Jiangxi Age: 20 Rank: 2 no.78. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tian Guang'en, 1880; R2-43; Province: Henan Age: 32 Rank: 3 no.165. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Guozhen, 1880; R2-45; Province: Guangdong Age: 27 Rank: 2 no.44. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Jiashu, 1880; R2-44; Province: Guangdong Age: 35 Rank: 2 no.71. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Duan Lin, 1883; R2-46; Province: Yunnan Age: 25 Rank: 3 no.164. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Yinrong, 1883; R2-41; Province: Guizhou Age: 24 Rank: 3 no.86 (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Yinluan, 1883; R2-47; Province: Zhili Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.106. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liu Sicheng, 1883; R2-48; Province: Jiangxi Age: 39 Rank: 3 no.176. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Rao Changlin, 1883; R2-49; Province: Jiangxi Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.35. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Baolian, 1883; R2-51; Province: Shanxi Age: 33 Rank: 3 no.22. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Xiangzhou, 1883; R2-52; Province: Guizhou Age: 26 Rank: 3 no.111. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Mianwen, 1883; R2-53; Province: White Banner Age: 37 Rank: 2 no.60. (Box 19)
  - Exam Year: Name: Deshou, 1886; R2-54; Province: Red Banner Age: 29 Rank: 3 no.181. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Duan, 1886; R2-55; Province: Guizhou Age: 34 Rank: 2 no.41. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Shaozeng, 1886; R2-56; Province: Jiangxi Age: 43 Rank: 3 no.165. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Shi Jinghuang, 1886; R2-57; Province: Anhui Age: 45 Rank: 3 no.8. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Mingde, 1886; R2-50; Province: Hubei Age: 29 Rank: 2 no.109 (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wen Jie, 1886; R2-58; Province: Hubei Age: 47 Rank: 3 no.131. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cheng Yulin, 1889; R2-59; Province: Guizhou Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.33. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Peng Guangzhan, 1889; R2-61; Province: Guangdong Age: 44 Rank: 3 no.44. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiong Wentao, 1889; R2-62; Province: Hubei Age: 39 Rank: 3 no.122. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Erchui, 1889; R2-63; Province: Blue Banner Age: 39 Rank: 2 no.76. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lu Daoxiang, 1890; R2-60; Province: Jiangxi Age: 28 Rank: 3 no.103 (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Qixu, 1890; R2-64; Province: Guizhou Age: 37 Rank: 2 no.131. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Zhonghao, 1890; R2-65; Province: Guizhou Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.104. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Xieyang, 1890; R2-66; Province: Yunnan Age: 24 Rank: 3 no.89. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Sun Bingyang, 1890; R2-67; Province: Guizhou Age: 35 Rank: 2 no.68. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Longzhao, 1890; R2-68; Province: Hunan Age: 43 Rank: 3 no.75. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Xiaocheng, 1890; R2-69; Province: Guangxi Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.19. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xu Jinqi, 1890; R2-70; Province: Guangxi Age: 28 Rank: 3 no.24. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yang Tingchun, 1890; R2-71; Province: Guizhou Age: 32 Rank: 2 no.41. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yu Guanji, 1890; R2-72; Province: Zhejiang Age: 33 Rank: 3 no.85. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Weixi, 1890; R2-73; Province: Jiangxi Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.65. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhu Zhanting, 1890; R2-74; Province: Fengtian Age: 33 Rank: 2 no.49. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Jian, 1890; R2-75; Province: Yunnan Age: 28 Rank: 3 no.183. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: You Sanli, 1892; R2-76; Province: Jiangxi Age: 25 Rank: 3 no.180. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Yu, 1892; R2-77; Province: Jiangxi Age: 31 Rank: 2 no.48. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Liangbi, 1892; R2-78; Province: Hunan Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.18. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liu Zhongqiong, 1892; R2-78b; Province: Guizhou Age: 32 Rank: 3 no.116. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lin Guogeng, 1892; R2-79; Province: Guangdong Age: 38 Rank: 2 no.32. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Hu Jihuan, 1892; R2-81; Province: Anhui Age: 35 Rank: 2 no.26. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Cunzhi, 1892; R2-82; Province: Jiangxi Age: 37 Rank: 3 no.83. (Box 20)
  - Exam Year: Name: Liang Yuwen, 1894; R2-80; Province: Zhili Age: 44 Rank: 3 no.136 (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Jingxing, 1894; R2-84; Province: Guizhou Age: 44 Rank: 3 no.123. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cheng Youqi, 1894; R2-85; Province: Guangdong Age: 36 Rank: 2 no.82. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Dai Yongqing, 1894; R2-86; Province: Yunnan Age: 36 Rank: 3 no.173. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Fan Rong, 1894; R2-87; Province: Sichuan Age: 39 Rank: 2 no.59. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Shen Tongfang, 1894; R2-88; Province: Jiangsu Age: 23 Rank: 3 no.68. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Hong, 1894; R2-89; Province: Guizhou Age: 40 Rank: 3 no.58. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zheng Yulin, 1894; R2-90; Province: Guizhou Age: 26 Rank: 3 no.176. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Bai Zizhao, 1895; R2-91; Province: Guizhou Age: 40 Rank: 3 no.181. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Kan, 1895; R3-1; Province: Henan Age: 37 Rank: 3 no.93. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Gao Songsheng, 1895; R3-2; Province: Jiangxi Age: 40 Rank: 3 no.42. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Shen Tong, 1895; R3-3; Province: Zhejiang Age: 40 Rank: 2 no.62. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Zhi'ang, 1895; R3-4; Province: Shanxi Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.150. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xie Xin, 1895; R3-5; Province: Shaanxi Age: 22 Rank: 2 no.25. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yang Enyuan, 1895; R3-6; Province: Guizhou Age: 17 Rank: 2 no.79. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Zhi'an, 1895; R3-7; Province: Guizhou Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.109. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Jiahui, 1895; R3-8; Province: Guizhou Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.52. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhu Yuanshan, 1895; R3-9; Province: Guangxi Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.90. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ren Chengji, 1898; R3-10; Province: Guizhou Age: 35 Rank: 3 no.84 (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Luchun, 1898; R3-11; Province: Jiangxi Age: 40 Rank: 2 no.83. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Mingke, 1898; R3-12; Province: Hubei Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.53. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Ding Shuqi, 1903; R2-83; Province: Guizhou Age: 28 Rank: 3 no.129 (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Banjiben, 1903; R3-13; Province: Blue Banner Age: 23 Rank: 3 no.109. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Guoxiang, 1903; R3-14; Province: Guizhou Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.131. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cheng Changnai, 1903; R3-15; Province: Jiangsu Age: 25 Rank: 3 no.37. (Box 21)
  - Exam Year: Name: Fang Luzhong, 1903; R3-16; Province: Anhui Age: 30 Rank: 2 no.112. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Huabing, 1903; R3-17; Province: Shanxi Age: 38 Rank: 2 no.103. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Shenwu, 1903; R3-18; Province: Shanxi Age: 35 Rank: 3 no.172. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Niu Zeshen, 1903; R3-19; Province: Zhejiang Age: 38 Rank: 2 no.120. (Box 22)